blogshares.com 2011-06-04

# Privacy Policy | BlogShares Help System

System Time: 11:06 04 Jun 2011 - 2 Players Online

Category: Official Pages

This is an **official** BlogShares Help System Page.  
Only BlogShares Admins or Users with appropriate Official Roles may edit it.

## Contents

  * 1 Information About Our Organization and Website
  * 2 Providing Visitors With Anonymous Access
  * 3 Automatic Collection of Information
  * 4 Data Collection and Purpose Specification
  * 5 Children's Privacy
  * 6 Confidentiality / Security
  * 7 Privacy Compliance
  * 8 Privacy Support

##  Information About Our Organization and Website 

Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organization like BlogShares. 

We are based in the the United States. 

Our principal activity is: Fantasy Stock Market Game 

Our privacy policy covers BlogShares and its web site. 

Organization Name: BlogShares 

Controller: Santa Cruz Tech 

Websites(s): [http://www.blogshares.com](http://www.blogshares.com/ "http://www.blogshares.com")

##  Providing Visitors With Anonymous Access 

You can access our Website home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data. Certain data is logged for security reasons and we reserve the right to retain such data indefinitely. Valid information is necessary to signup for an account of the service provided to the user; we may retain this indefinitely, and disclose said data in the event of users abusing the system. The Services and Links of Our Website 

Our Website enables you to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. When you do so, other visitors may collect your data. 

Our Website does include links to third party Web service providers. 

##  Automatic Collection of Information 

We automatically log personal data by means such as programming or we link information automatically logged by such means with personal data about specific individuals. We do so for the following purposes: 

  * Technical administration of the Website 
  * Customer administration 
  * Facilitate playing the game 

We use cookies to store personal data or we link information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals. We do so for the following purposes: 

  * Technical administration of the Website 
  * Customer administration 
  * Facilitate playing the game 

##  Data Collection and Purpose Specification 

We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. 

We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations. 

We do collect website URLs and names from other sources such as Weblogs.com ([http://www.weblogs.com](http://www.weblogs.com/ "http://www.weblogs.com")) 

##  Children's Privacy 

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children. 

We do not take specific steps to protect the privacy of children who disclose their personal data to us. 

We do provide information about our personal data practices in relation to children on our home page and wherever we knowingly collect personal data from children on our Website. Disclosure and Visitor Choice 

We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organizations, except in the case of abuse. 

##  Confidentiality / Security 

We do not give visitors to our Website the option of using a secure transmission method to send us their personal data. 

We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal data, but will give reasons for our refusal. 

##  Privacy Compliance 

There are no national laws or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our website or organization. 

There are no global or regional regulatory or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our website or organization. 

##  Privacy Support 

If you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact: support@blogshares.com. 

We do not recommend another means by which visitors' concerns may be addressed.
